const movie_data = {
    avengers : {
        id: 1,
        title : "Avengers",
        total : 5,
        questions:[
            {
                id:1,
                question:"How many rings does Captain America's shield have?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : 2
            },
            {
                id:2,
                question:"What planet was the Soul Stone hidden on in the movie Infinity War?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : "Vormir"
            },
            {
                id:3,
                question:"What is the real name of the Incredible Hulk?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : "Bruce Banner"
            },
            {
                id:4,
                question:"Who took out Tony Stark's parents?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : "Winter Soldier"
            },
            {
                id:5,
                question:"How many rings does Captain America's shield have?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : 2
            }
        ]
    },
    moneyheist :{
        id: 2,
        title : "Money Heist",
        total : 5,
        questions:[
            
                {
                    id:1,
                    question:" How long did the professor take to prepare for the robbery?",
                    options:{
                        "a": 3,
                        "b": 2,
                        "c": 4,
                        "d": 5
                    },
                    answer : "years"
                },
                {
                    id:2,
                    question:"How many people did the professor recruit to help him carry out his plan?",
                    options:{
                        "a": 3,
                        "b": 2,
                        "c": 4,
                        "d": 5
                    },
                    answer : "eight"
                },
                {
                    id:3,
                    question:"Inspector Raquel's mother suffered from which medical condition?",
                    options:{
                        "a": 3,
                        "b": 2,
                        "c": 4,
                        "d": 5
                    },
                    answer : "Alzheimer's disease"
                },
                {
                    id:4,
                    question:"The whole idea and plan of the heist was whose?",
                    options:{
                        "a": 3,
                        "b": 2,
                        "c": 4,
                        "d": 5
                    },
                    answer : "The professor's father"
                },
                {
                    id:5,
                    question:"How much money were the Robbers able to print?",
                    options:{
                        "a": 3,
                        "b": 2,
                        "c": 4,
                        "d": 5
                    },
                    answer : "984 million Euros"
                }
            
        ]
    },
    friends:{
        id:3,
        title: "Friends",
        total : 5,
        questions:[
            {
                id:1,
                question:"How many sisters does Joey have?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : 7
            },
            {
                id:2,
                question:"What is the name of Joey’s character in the commercial for opening milk cartons?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : "Kevin"
            },
            {
                id:3,
                question:"What is Ross’ profession?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : "Palaeontologist"
            },
            {
                id:4,
                question:"Where does Ross spend the night with Emily after they first meet?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : "A bed and breakfast in Vermont"
            },
            {
                id:5,
                question:"What song does Ross’ monkey, Marcel, keep playing?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : "‘The Lion Sleeps Tonight‘ by The Tokens"
            }
        ]
    },
    squidgame:{
        id:4,
        title: "Squid game",
        total : 5,
        questions:[
            {
                id:1,
                question:"How many contestants show up to play Squid Game?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : 456
            },
            {
                id:2,
                question:"What shape did the old man carve in the Honeycomb challenge?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : "star"
            },
            {
                id:3,
                question:"Who was Hwang Jun-ho looking for?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : "His older brother"
            },
            {
                id:4,
                question:"How many games are in the competition?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : 6
            },
            {
                id:5,
                question:"Where are the contestants held?",
                options:{
                    "a": 3,
                    "b": 2,
                    "c": 4,
                    "d": 5
                },
                answer : "An Island in South Korea"
            }
        ]
    }
}

export default movie_data;
